[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to King Kong at the end of the 1933 movie King Kong?", "correct_answer": "He gets killed.", "incorrect_answers": ["He finds a mate and they live happily ever after.", "They put him in a zoo.", "He runs away."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What creature is sent to kill James Bond in Dr. No?", "correct_answer": "Tarantula", "incorrect_answers": ["Crocodile", "Gorilla", "Snake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Knightfall storyline, Bruce Wayne finally meets his match in the hulking villain Bane, who fatally injures him, thus causing him to be replaced by Azreal, who becomes the new Batman.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinctive feature does the villain in The Man with the Golden Gun have?", "correct_answer": "A third nipple", "incorrect_answers": ["A sixth finger", "A single nostril", "A third eyebrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scientists have proved that one of the health dangers, which ingesting sugar on a habitual basis involves, is the suppression of the activity of which system of the human body?", "correct_answer": "Immune system", "incorrect_answers": ["Sensory system", "Reproductive system", "Cardiovascular system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the British sitcom about the Home Guard during World War II?", "correct_answer": "Dads Army", "incorrect_answers": ["McHales Navy", "Fathers Flyboys", "Pops Platoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this line delivered by Virgil Cole in the 2008 western Appaloosa: I enforce the law. Killing is sometimes a __________.", "correct_answer": "byproduct", "incorrect_answers": ["necessity", "pleasure", "perk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marine algae may have this effect on the human body.", "correct_answer": "Laxative effect", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "May act as opiates", "Increase the cholesterol levels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which three actors played the members of Fred Millers gang in the western movie High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Shep Wooley, Lee Van Cleef, Robert J. Wilke", "incorrect_answers": ["Otto Kruger, Morgan Farley, Dale Robertson", "Thomas Mitchell, Ian McHenry, Vincent Fleming", "Harry Morgan, Lon Chaney, Jr., Lloyd Bridges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The main character in the movie My Big Fat Greek Wedding, Toula, has a father named Gus. He thinks Pine Sol will cure any illness and carries it around all the time, spraying it on wounds.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What development revolutionized the extraction of espresso?", "correct_answer": "The pump", "incorrect_answers": ["The conical burr coffee grinder", "The aluminum coffee tamp", "Reverse osmosis water filtration"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year does the storyline of Watchmen take place?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1876", "1990", "1972"]}]